Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 1 and District 1 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 1 Locals, 2.
  - Local 128
    - Local 128 Outgoing Correspondence, 1946-1952 (Box 8, Folder 113)
      - Price to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 17,1952; 17.
      - Richard Rau to Ratner Regarding Finances, October 31, 1950; 18.
      - Rau to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 16, 1950; 19.
      - Kathryn Schlenker to UE Regarding Finances with Telephone Bill and Ratner Memo to Ernest Moyer, September 9, 1950; 20.
      - Schlenker to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 21, 1950; 21.
      - Schlenker to Emspak Regarding Local 128 Christmas Party, December 11, 1950; 22.
      - Schlenker to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 128 Christmas Party, December 11, 1950; 23.
      - Schlenker to Matles Regarding Local 128 Christmas Party, December 11, 1950; 24.
      - Schlenker to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 15, 1951; 25.
      - Schlenker to Emspak Regarding Finances with Telephone Bill, May 23, 1951; 26.
      - Schlenker to Emspak Regarding Strike at International Harvester, October 30, 1952; 27.
      - Schlenker to Emspak Regarding Strike at International Harvester, November 20, 1952; 28.
      - Sally Smith to Emspak Regarding Strike at International Harvester, October 15, 1952; 29.
      - Smith to Emspak Regarding Strike at International Harvester, October 30, 1952; 30.
      - Althea Stewart to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, April 1947; 31.
      - Vassel Thamel to Ratner Regarding Finances, April 15, 1950; 32.
      - Olga Wallach to UE Regarding Finances, October 28, 1948; 33.
      - Wallach to Janet Barrish Regarding Staff Finances, February 18, 1949; 34.
      - Wallach to Ratner Regarding Finances, April 1, 1949; 35.
    - Local 128 Receipts, Harry Block, August 23, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Local 128 Supply Requisitions, Harry Block, August 1, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Local 128 Notice of Shipment, Harry Block, August 4, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Local 128 Notices of Delinquency/Suspension, 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 117)
      - Delinquency, December 1937; 1.
      - Suspension, February 2, 1938; 2.
    - Local 128 Financial Miscellaneous, 1939-1953 (Box 8, Folder 118)
      - Notice of Strike Stamps Shipment, August 4, 1939; 1.
      - Bonding Receipt, July 11, 1947; 2.
      - Substitution Card, October 9, 1947-March 8, 1948; 3.
      - General Office Statement, December 22, 1953; 4.
    - Local 128 Organization, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 119)
      - Ernest Moyer to Julius Emspak, August 26, 1946; 1.
      - Secretary of Emspak to Joseph Infante, August 27, 1946; 2.
      - Emspak to Moyer, September 19, 1946; 3.
      - James Matles to Emspak, October 19, 1946; 4.
    - Local 128 Garnet Chemical Strike, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 120)
      - Julius Emspak to Gene Derrickson, March 7, 1951; 1.
      - Derrickson to Emspak, March 12, 1951; 2.
      - Derrickson to Emspak, April 6, 1951; 3.
      - Emspak to Derrickson, April 10, 1951; 4.
      - Lillian Rosenberg to Derrickson, May 29, 1951; 5.
      - Derrickson to Rosenberg, June 1, 1951; 6.
      - Nat Spero to Derrickson, June 7, 1951; 7.
    - Local 128 Newspapers, UE 128 News Bulletin, November 1, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Local 128 Leaflets, "UE Local 128", 1951 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Local 128 Newspaper Clippings, Lehigh Valley Labor Herald, August 28, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Local 128 Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Local 128 Black and Decker Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Local 129 (Pine Grove)
    - Local 129 (Pine Grove) Incoming Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Herman Harvey Regarding Local 129 Organization, November 16, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Local 129 (Pine Grove) Receipts, Norman B. Wonnmeyer, December 27, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Local 129 (Pine Grove) Per Capita Reports, December 20, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Local 129 (Pine Grove) Finances, Inter-Office Memo Regarding Returned Supplies, March 2 (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Local 129 (Wilkes Barre)
    - Local 129 (Wilkes Barre) Officers Lists, March 28, 1947-January 22, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Local 129 (Wilkes Barre) Incoming Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 131)
      - Julius Emspak to Agnes Broderick Regarding Local 129 Organization, March 20, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Broderick Regarding Local 129 Organization, March 28, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to Broderick Regarding Local 129 Organization, May 2, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Ruth Ruddick Regarding Local 129 Organization, May 22, 1947; 4.
      - Emspak to Rose Shea Regarding PAC, February 6, 1948; 5.
      - Emspak to Broderick Regarding Finances, July 30, 1948; 6.
    - Local 129 (Wilkes Barre) Outgoing Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 8, Folder 132)
      - Agnes Broderick to James Matles Regarding Organization, March 13, 1947; 1.
      - Broderick Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, April 30, 1947; 2.
      - Broderick to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 129 Collective Bargaining and Strike at Teleradio, February 26, 1948; 3.
      - Ruth Ruddick Telegram to Emspak Regarding Address Change, November 17, 1949; 4.
      - Ruddick to Emspak Regarding Local 129 Seperation, November 27, 1947; 5.
      - Rose Shea to Emspak Regarding United Packinghouse Workers Strike, January 17, 1949; 6.
      - Agnes Worga to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 21, 1948; 7.
    - Local 129 (Wilkes Barre) Charter, Wilkes Barre Teleradio Engineering Corporation, March 28, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Local 129 (Wilkes Barre) Charter, 1946-1947 (Box 8, Folder 134)
      - Julius Emspak to Peter Besch, November 27, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to James Price, January 9, 1947; 2.
      - Price to Emspak, January 13, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Price, February 14, 1947; 4.
      - Emspak to Price, March 28, 1947; 5.
      - Emspak to Jack Gorelick, March 28, 1947; 6.
      - Gorelick to Emspak, April 27, 1947; 7.
      - Report on Application of Teleradio Workers for a Supreme Charter, 1947; 8.
    - Local 129 (Wilkes Barre) Leaflet, "Wage Cuts!", January 10, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Local 130
    - Local 130 Officers Lists, October 22, 1942-March 11, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Local 130 Incoming Correspondence, 1939-1954 (Box 8, Folder 137)
      - Julius Emspak to Edward Rattell Regarding Finances, February 4, 1939; 1.
      - Emspak to Rattell, April 17, 1939; 2.
      - Emspak to Rattell Regarding Unemployment and Supplies, August 14, 1939; 3.
      - Emspak to Rattell Regarding Finances, August 16, 1939; 4.
      - Emspak to Paul Cummings Regarding Finances, November 9, 1939; 5.
      - Emspak to Cummings Regarding Finances, February 13, 1940; 6.
      - Emspak to Cummings Regarding Supplies, March 18, 1940; 7.
      - Emspak to Cummings Regarding Supplies, March 19, 1940; 8.
      - Emspak to Cummings Regarding Supplies, April 4, 1940; 9.
      - Emspak to Cummings Regarding Supplies, April 17, 1940; 10.
      - Emspak to Cummings Regarding Supplies, April 30, 1940; 11.
      - Emspak to Cummings Regarding Supplies, May 16, 1940; 12.
      - Emspak to Cummings Regarding Supplies, May 23, 1940; 13.
      - Emspak to Cummings Regarding Supplies, June 11, 1940; 14.
      - Emspak to Cummings Regarding Finances, June 22, 1940; 15.
      - Emspak to Cummings Regarding Finances, August 20, 1940; 16.
      - Emspak to Cummings Regarding Finances, October 17, 1940; 17.
      - Emspak to Frank Gledrich Regarding Mailing List, December 30, 1940; 18.
      - Emspak to Gledrich Regarding Mailing List, February 5, 1941; 19.
      - Emspak to Gledrich Regarding Finances with 1940-1941 Financial Records, September 16, 1941; 20.
      - Emspak to Gledrich Regarding Mailing List, December 11, 1941; 21.
      - Emspak to Rueben Dietz Regarding Finances, October 20, 1942; 22.
      - Emspak to Lyndon Pratt Regarding Finances, May 18, 1943; 23.
      - Emspak to J. Mahoney Regarding Finances, February 14, 1944; 24.
      - Emspak to Gledrich Regarding Finances, July 13, 1945; 25.
      - Emspak to Gledrich Regarding Local 130 Strike at Westinghouse, March 19, 1946; 26.
      - Emspak to John Green Regarding Local 130 Strike at Westinghouse, April 20, 1946; 27.
      - Emspak to William Long Regarding Local 130 Strike at Westinghouse, April 26, 1946; 28.
      - Emspak to Gledrich Regarding Local 130 Strike at Westinghouse, May 3, 1946; 29.
      - Emspak to Gledrich Regarding Local 130 Strike at Westinghouse, May 10, 1946; 30.
      - Emspak to Gledrich Regarding Local 130 Strike at Westinghouse, May 17, 1946; 31.
      - Emspak to Long Regarding Finances, August 27, 1946; 32.
      - Emspak to Gordon Shipley Regarding PAC, October 15, 1947; 33.
      - Emspak to Shipley Regarding PAC, November 6, 1947; 34.
      - Emspak to Shipley Regarding PAC, December 17, 1947; 35.
      - Emspak to Herbert Nichol Regarding Finances, November 9, 1950; 36.
      - Emspak to Eugene Watts Regarding Finances, December 15, 1950; 37.
      - Emspak to Watts Regarding Finances, July 31, 1951; 38.
      - Emspak to Watts Regarding Finances, October 9, 1951; 39.
      - Emspak to Charles Johnson Regarding Strike Fund, November 28, 1952; 40.
      - Emspak to James Carr Regarding Finances, February 8, 1954; 41.
      - Secretary of Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Supplies, November 22, 1943; 42.
      - Fitzgerald to Watts Regarding Joint Meeting of Baltimore Locals, March 23, 1949; 43.
      - Fitzgerald to Watts Regarding Membership Meeting, April 11, 1950; 44.
      - James Matles to Watts Regarding National Labor Relations Board Elections for Westinghouse Baltimore, November 19, 1951; 45.
      - Matles to Watts Regarding Finances, December 17, 1951; 46.
      - Matles to Watts Regarding Staff Finances, May 5, 1953; 47.
      - Matles to Watts Regarding Political Action, August 11, 1954; 48.
      - Edward Matthews to Pratt Regarding Dues Check-off, December 29, 1943; 49.
      - Don Pinkston to Donald Stanfield Regarding Publicity, February 6, 1946; 50.
    - Local 130 Outgoing Correspondence, 1939-1952 (Box 8, Folder 138)
      - Paul Cummings to Julius Emspak Regarding Membership, December 1939; 1.
      - Cummings to Emspak Regarding Membership and Unemployment, January 1940; 2.
      - Cummings to Emspak Regarding Supplies, January 1940; 3.
      - Cummings to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 1940; 4.
      - Cummings to Emspak Regarding Membership, March 28, 1940; 5.
      - Cummings to UE Regarding Supplies, March 1940; 6.
      - Cummings to Emspak Regarding Supplies and Membership, April 1940; 7.
      - Cummings to Emspak Regarding Supplies, May 1940; 8.
      - Frank Giedrich to Emspak Regarding Finances, September 9, 1941; 9.
      - Giedrich to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 14, 1941; 10.
      - Giedrich to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 11, 1945; 11.
      - Melvin Grahl Telegram to James Matles Regarding Local 130 Contract at Westinghouse Baltimore, Wages, and Pensions, July 22, 1953; 12.
      - William Hill to Emspak Regarding PAC, October 10, 1947; 13.
      - Hill to Emspak Regarding PAC, December 30, 1947; 14.
      - Thomas Hughes to UE Regarding Dues Check-off and Finances, October 13, 1943; 15.
      - Richard Linsley to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, November 27, 1940; 16.
      - William Long to Harry Block Regarding Finances, April 19, 1946; 17.
      - Long to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 22, 1946; 18.
      - William McHale to Emspak Regarding 1944 UE Convention, December 26, 1944; 19.
      - J.P. Mahoney to Emspak Regarding Local 130 Officers, September 14, 1944; 20.
      - George Murray to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 17, 1945; 21.
      - Jack Meyers to Emspak Regarding Finances, War Labor Board, and Local 138 Collective Bargaining at Zallea Brothers Johnson, October 16, 1942; 22.
      - Meyers to UE Regarding Local 130 Strike at Westinghouse and White Collar Workers, January 22, 1946; 23.
      - Herbert Nichol to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 3, 1950; 24.
      - Lyndon Pratt to UE Regarding Supplies, November 16, 1943; 25.
      - Pratt to UE Regarding Dues Check-off, December 1, 1943; 26.
      - Pratt to Emspak Regarding Dues Check-off, December 28, 1943; 27.
      - Pratt to UE News Regarding Amalgamations of Local 1207/Local 130 and Local 1207/Local 1227, July 30, 1943; 28.
      - Edward Rattell to Emspak Regarding Dues, January 30, 1939; 29.
      - Rattell to Emspak Regarding Dues, February 1, 1939; 30.
      - Rattell to Emspak Regarding Supplies with March 23, 1939, Credit/Bill, March 21, 1939; 31.
      - Rattell to Emspak Regarding Dues, April 27, 1939; 32.
      - Rattell to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 18, 1939; 33.
      - Rattell to Emspak Regarding Finances, September 10, 1939; 34.
      - Gordon Shipley to Emspak Regarding Local 130 Officers, June 27, 1947; 35.
      - Shipley to Emspak Regarding Dues Check-off, February 16, 1950; 36.
      - Donald Stansfield to Emspak Regarding Publicity, February 5, 1946; 37.
      - William Sykora Card to Edward Matthews Regarding Local 130 Elections and Factionalism with 1943 UE Convention Delegates Election Results, July 29, 1943; 38.
      - Eugene Watts to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Collective Bargaining at Westinghouse, March 17, 1949; 39.
      - Watts to Emspak Regarding UE News and National Labor Relations Board Elections for Westinghouse Baltimore, February 21, 1950; 40.
      - Watts to Fitzgerald Regarding NLRB Elections at Westinghouse, April 5, 1950; 41.
      - Watts to Emspak Regarding Finances with December 1, 1950, Check, November 9, 1950; 42.
      - Watts to Emspak Regarding Finances with Bank Returned Slip, November 9, 1950; 43.
      - Watts to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 24, 1951; 44.
      - Watts to Emspak, May 13, 1952; 45.
      - Jack Zucker to James Matles Regarding Factionalism and Local 130 Elections for UE Convention Delegates with "Dear Member" Leaflet, July 8, 1947; 46.
    - Local 130 Salary/Expense Letters, Frank Giedrick, December 13, 1940-January 9, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Local 130 Receipts, Edward Rattell, December 20, 1938-October 13, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - Local 130 Receipts, H.R. Walsh, September 20, 1938-November 9, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Local 130 Receipts, Paul Cummings, November 8, 1939-August 31, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Local 130 Per Capita Reports, September 8, 1938-August 12, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - Local 130 Supply Requisitions, 1938-1940 (Box 8, Folder 144)
      - E. Rattell, December 21, 1938-March 20, 1939; 1-4.
      - Paul Cummings, November 10, 1939-August 21, 1940; 5-13.
    - Local 130 Stamps, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 145)
      - Edward Rattell, February 3-August 14, 1939; 1-4.
      - Paul Cummings, December 8, 1939-May 23, 1940; 5-8.
    - Local 130 Finances, 1951, undated (Box 8, Folder 146)
      - Refund on Per Capita Report Overpayment, May 1, 1951; 1.
      - Local 130 Charter, n.d.; 2.
    - Local 130 Per Capita, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 147)
      - Gene Derrickson to Julius Emspak, August 30, 1951; 1.
      - James Matles to Herbert Nichol, October 9, 1951; 2.
      - Exerpt of Letter from Derrickson, November 6, 1951; 3.
      - Janet Memo to Matles, November 7, 1951; 4.
      - Derrickson to Matles, November 8, 1951; 5.
      - Matles to Derrickson, November 8, 1951; 6.
      - Matles to Derrickson, November 19, 1951; 7.
    - Local 130 Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 148)
      - E.L.M. Memo to Pete Abbond Regarding Finances and Westinghouse Conference Board, June 21, 1955; 1.
      - E.L.M. Memo to James Matles Regarding Local 130 Strike at Westinghouse Baltimore and IUE Inter-union Relations, December 5, 1955; 2.
    - Local 130 Newspapers, The United Front, June 17, 1940-January 9, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 149)
    - Local 130 Newspapers, Transmitter, June 16, 1941-June 1, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 150)
    - Local 130 Leaflets, 1942, undated (Box 8, Folder 151)
      - "A Call to Arms!", 1942; 1.
      - "Bendix Workers", 2.
  - Local 131
    - Local 131 Officer Lists, July 12, 1940-April 30, 1949, undated (Box 8, Folder 152)
    - Local 131 Incoming Correspondence, 1938-1951, undated (Box 8, Folder 153)
      - Julius Emspak to Carl Bersing Regarding Finances, October 3, 1938; 1.
      - Emspak to Bersing Regarding Supplies, October 18, 1938; 2.
      - Emspak to Alfred Egge Regarding Supplies, October 18, 1938; 3.
      - Emspak to Bersing Regarding Finances, October 20, 1938; 4.
      - Emspak to Harry Block Regarding Finances, November 21, 1938; 5.
      - Emspak to Robert Gress, June 7, 1939; 6.
      - Secretary of Emspak to John Pastir Regarding UE News, October 10, 1939; 7.
      - Emspak to Alfred Egge Regarding Finances, October 19, 1939; 8.
      - Emspak to Alfred Egge Regarding Local 131 Constitution, February 20, 1940; 9.
      - Emspak to Alfred Egge Regarding Finances, April 18, 1940; 10.
      - Emspak to Alfred Egge Regarding Supplies, July 17, 1940; 11.
      - Emspak to Harold Egge Regarding Finances, October 14, 1940; 12.
      - Emspak to Harold Egge Regarding Mailing List, December 30, 1940; 13.
      - Emspak to Roman Kadysciewsi Regarding Mailing List, July 29, 1941; 14.
      - Emspak to Kadysciewski Regarding Mailing List and Finances, August 14, 1941; 15.
      - Emspak to Kadysciewski Regarding Finances, August 27, 1941; 16.
      - Emspak to Anna Trefny Regarding Officers' Report, October 10, 1941; 17.
      - Emspak to Pauline Petruno, November 15, 1943; 18.
      - Emspak to Kadysciewski Regarding Veterans, May 28, 1945; 19.
      - Emspak to Constance Laurence, October 2, 1950; 20.
      - Emspak to Gene Derrickson Regarding Local 131 Suspension Notice, May 28, 1951; 21.
      - David Ratner Memo to Meyer Harbus, n.d.; 22.
    - Local 131 Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1951, undated (Box 8, Folder 154)
      - Carl Bersing to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, September 30, 1938; 1.
      - Bersing to James Matles Regarding Local 131 Contract at Edison Splitdorf, September 29, 1941; 2.
      - Bersing to Emspak Regarding 1941 Officers' Report, October 9, 1941; 3.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, October 14, 1938; 4.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, November 28, 1938; 5.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, December 24, 1938; 6.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, January 14, 1939; 7.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, February 6, 1939; 8.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, February 17, 1939; 9.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, March 18, 1939; 10.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, April 20, 1939; 11.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, May 20, 1939; 12.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, June 19, 1939; 13.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, July 18, 1939; 14.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, August 15, 1939; 15.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, September 18, 1939; 16.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, October 6, 1939; 17.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, October 18, 1939; 18.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, October 19, 1939; 19.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, November 18, 1939; 20.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, December 15, 1939; 21.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding "Trade Union Facts" with Receipts, January 3, 1940; 22.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, January 15, 1940; 23.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, February 18, 1940; 24.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, March 17, 1940; 25.
      - Alfred Egge to UE Regarding Finances, April 17, 1940; 26.
      - Harold Egge to Matles Regarding Wages, April 5, 1939; 27.
      - Harold Egge to Emspak Regarding Officers' Report, October 3, 1939; 28.
      - Harold Egge to Emspak Regarding Constitution, February 8, 1940; 29.
      - Harold Egge to UE Regarding Finances, May 18, 1940; 30.
      - Harold Egge to UE Regarding Finances, June 15, 1940; 31.
      - Harold Egge to UE Regarding Finances, August 20, 1940; 32.
      - Robert Gress to UE Regarding Unemployment, June 5, 1939; 33.
      - Roman Kadyscieski to UE Regarding Membership and Finances, July 19, 1941; 34.
      - Kadyscieski to UE Regarding Finances, July 29, 1941; 35.
      - Kadyscieski to UE Regarding Membership and Finances, August 1941; 36.
      - Kadyscieski to UE Regarding Unemployment and Women, July 1942; 37.
      - Kadyscieski to UE Regarding Finances, December 19, 1948; 38.
      - Kadyscieski to UE Regarding Finances, August 18, 1945; 39.
      - Kadyscieski to UE Regarding Veterans and Finances, 40.
      - Kadyscieski to UE Regarding Finances, n.d.; 41.
      - Edward Koloski to UE Regarding Finances, July 9, 1940; 42.
      - Koloski to Emspak Regarding Supplies, July 31, 1940; 43.
      - John Pastir to Emspak Regarding UE News, October 10, 1939; 44.
      - Samuel Pavlovich to UE Regarding PAC, October 7, 1946; 45.
      - Pauline Petruno to UE Regarding Overtime and Executive Order 9240, November 1943; 46.
      - James Price to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 4, 1951; 47.
    - Local 131 Salary/Expense Letters, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 155)
      - Harold Egge, February 18, 1941; 1.
      - Roman Kadysciewski, July 28-August 19, 1941; 2-3.
    - Local 131 Receipts, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 156)
      - Alfred Egge, October 18, 1939-April 22, 1940; 1-21.
      - Harold Egge, May 20-August 22, 1940; 22-25.
    - Local 131 Per Capita Reports, November 28, 1938-August 20, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 157)
    - Local 131 Supply Requisitions, 1938-1940 (Box 8, Folder 158)
      - Carl Bersing, September 30, 1938; 1.
      - Alfred Egge, February 6, 1939-February 16, 1940; 2-6.
      - Harold Egge, July 18, 1940; 7.
      - Edward Rolosky, August 1, 1940; 8.
    - Local 131 Stamps, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 159)
      - Carl Bersing, October 6, 1938; 1.
      - Alfred Egge, September 26, 1939; 2.
    - Local 131 Notices of Shipment, 1938-1940 (Box 8, Folder 160)
      - Carl Bersing, October 3, 1938; 1.
      - Alfred Egge, April 24, 1939-February 26, 1940; 2-6.
      - Edward Kolosky, August 12, 1940; 7.
    - Local 131 Notices of Delinquency/Suspension, November 1938-April 1951 (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Local 131 Finances, 1940-1955 (Box 8, Folder 162)
      - Charter, September 28, 1938; 1.
      - Application for Bond Coverage, July 8, 1939; 2.
      - National Surety Corporation, Underwriter in Fidelity Bond, July 11, 1939; 3.
      - Certificate, August 15, 1940; 4.
      - Redemptive Advice, U.S. Savings Bonds with Request Form for Payment of U.S. Savings Bond, April 29, 1955; 5.
    - Local 131 Disbanded Local, 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 163)
  - Local 132
    - Local 132 Officers Lists, February 19, 1944-June 6, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Local 132 Membership Resolutions Regarding Disbanding with August 28, 1950, Julius Emspak Letter to Henry Rhine, August 1950 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Local 132 Incoming Correspondence, 1940-1950 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Neil Brant to Martin Sharley Regarding War Labor Board and Job Classification, March 26, 1945; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Harry Block Regarding Finances, January 24, 1940; 2.
      - Emspak to Clarence Hoffman Regarding Finances, April 4, 1940; 3.
      - Emspak to Hoffman Regarding Finances, April 11, 1940; 4.
      - Emspak to Hoffman Regarding Finances, June 14, 1940; 5.
      - Emspak to Hoffman Regarding Supplies, July 18, 1940; 6.
      - Emspak to Hoffman Regarding Mailing List, January 12, 1942; 7.
      - Emspak to Jacob Miller Regarding Publicity, January 3, 1943; 8.
      - Emspak to Martin K. Sharley Regarding Membership Meeting, January 8, 1943; 9.
      - Secretary of Emspak to Sharley, January 25, 1943; 10.